ifyoucan.org 2015-12-04

# Privacy Policy | If You Can

### IF... The Emotional IQ Game | Play. Learn. Grow. | Succeed at School, with Friends, in Life!

**Last Updated: 26th November 2013**

This Policy explains how personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by If You Can Company and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies (“If You Can” or “We”). This privacy policy (“Policy”) applies to the websites of If You Can, including [ifyoucan.org, and If You Can’s mobile applications (collectively, “Services”). This Policy does not apply to websites, applications or services that display or link to different privacy statements.

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect information users provide to us. For example, in our mobile app for children we collect limited non-personal information from children. We collect a character name, age of the child, and the child’s activities in the app. We also collect the email address of the child’s parent in our mobile app for children to provide notice to, and update the parent about their child’s participation.

When you visit our websites, some information is automatically collected. For example, when you visit our websites your computer’s operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language, and the website you visited before our site are logged automatically. We also collect information about your usage and activity on our websites.

**Cookies**. We may automatically collect information using “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Services and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our Services. When you visit our Site, our Site honors your Web browser signal and other similar mechanisms that indicate your request to disable tracking of your online activities over time and across different websites and online services.

**Web Beacons**. We may collect information using Web beacons. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our Services or in our emails. We use Web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

When you download and use our mobile applications, or access our websites from your mobile device, we may also log information related to your device and your usage of our applications. We may log your location, device type, serial number, device identifiers, the types and versions of mobile operating systems and software you use, and time-stamped logs of data exchanges.

#### USE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We only use the parent’s online contact information collected from their child’s mobile app to provide notice to, and update the parent about their child’s participation. The parent’s online contact information collected from the child’s mobile app will not be used or disclosed for any other purpose unless agreed to by the parent. Parents may refuse to permit their child’s participation in our service and may require the deletion of the parent’s online contact information, by contacting us at our information below.

We use personal information collected from parents through our Services for purposes described in this Policy or disclosed to you on our Services or in connection with our services. For example, we may use your information to:

  * update you about your child’s participation using our mobile app;
  * operate and improve our Services, products, and services;
  * understand you and your preferences to enhance your experience and enjoyment using our Services, products, and services;
  * process and deliver contest entries and rewards;
  * respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * provide and deliver products and services you request;
  * send you related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * communicate with you about new contests, promotions, and rewards, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by If You Can and our selected partners;
  * link or combine with other personal information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and
  * protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity.

If You Can may store and process personal information in the United States and other countries.

#### SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We do not share your personal information with third parties other than as follows:

  * with your consent, for example, when you agree to our sharing your information with other third parties for their own marketing purposes subject to their separate privacy policies;
  * with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who work for us and need access to your information to do that work;
  * to (i) comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process, (ii) to protect the rights and property of If You Can our agents, customers, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies, and terms of use or (iii) in an emergency to protect the personal safety of If You Can, its customers, or any person;
  * in connection with or during negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, transaction or proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture or disclosure of all or a portion of our business or assets to another company.  
We may also share aggregated or deidentified information.

#### SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

If You Can takes reasonable steps to help protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

#### YOUR INFORMATION CHOICES AND CHANGES

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from If You Can by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your accounts or our ongoing business relations. You may also send requests about your contact preferences, changes to your information including requests to opt-out of sharing your personal information with third parties by emailing helpme@ifyoucan.org.

Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Site.

#### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

If You Can may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the “Last Updated” date above.

#### QUESTIONS

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at [privacy@ifyoucan.org](mailto:privacy@ifyoucan.org?Subject=Privacy%20Question)
